You didn't raise your voice, you didn't raise your hand, just stood there quiet like you didn't understand, but I saw your eyes, you knew the shape of it, felt the air.
Second pause in the room reset someone laughs it off someone just forgets you call it be sick all the stage control
They said
I did have like a road mod hide everybody or like hide a lot of people
I could tell they did because like a lot of people had been here for a long time
So it had to be somebody going into old episodes and hiding everybody
Um, I did have to unmod some people and it's like so
I don't know. Hopefully got the right one
But it is kind of quiet in here still I mean, I don't I don't know
Last night, someone came in and said,
oh, go to a clumsy bean gang channel.
He wants you on the panel.
I go in there, all of a sudden, you're platforming a PD.
I said, OK, bye.
He also had the Terry Davis, horrible Terry Davis
person on that crystal and chat and stuff.
So it was an ambush, basically.
Yeah, I don't feel like going on a show and being ambushed.
No, thank you.
Thank you very much, but no, thank you.
If you're in the chat shout out shout out your birthday if you want me to read your birthday. You're just a month and day
For the birthday book today
I'm only gonna be on until probably nine in the morning my time and then I'll come back and be on again
But I got to go get cigars, and I don't have data on my phone right now for like the IRL stuff
Maybe later this week. Okay, but um, I
Don't know I mean it's like literally
This woman Crystal Ann, well I don't know, you know I just, I remember I played a clip of her like you know talking about
Bita and stuff like last year. It was kind of funny and then I got like your messages
Oh, don't play that Crystal Anna the one you play that blah blah blah and she and she always appears on YouTube
She sounds like she's
Still a little bit nutty, I don't know not to judge her too harshly, but
Literally like yesterday
To have like, you know, to talk about the issues going on and stuff for a couple hours
And that's perfectly normal to go on like for six seven eight hours about
Obsessing about PDF. I mean it's like
Wow, I mean it's like, that's gonna hurt someone's brain.
I mean, I understand like just like focusing on that,
like just so much, it's just like,
it's really weird and bizarre to me
and I don't know how they can just go for hours
and hours and hours and hours and hours
just talking about it.
And then in weird, like they're doing weird.
Fucking shit, like saying well, you know what we can start like our group and then it's like and then anybody that's against us
Is like we're gonna say that there's a PDF and then like you know
And then we're gonna be the best group and everyone's gonna be wanted want to be in our group
And it's like okay. Well, that's like the game plan for like a lot of groups like us nowadays, you know
It's like you can't like you imagine like you know if everyone
If every attorney that had to defend somebody, like it was innocent over some horrible charge
like this, you know, it was going to be smeared like that.
And, you know, it's like a really about silencing people and like, you know, hiding the real
truth and smearing people without having, they're having a recourse, really.
And that's like, you know, maybe they found an effective weapon, maybe it worked at some
point or another.
But I think people are smart enough now to like be more objective about things.
I'm not sure that they are, you know, I just like, you know, I
Maybe I put too much stock in like some of the human race
But I do believe that people can look for the truth
Everyone shout out at least hello or something or else you can just say I hate watching or something like that
Just reveal yourselves. You'll be revealed one way or another so
Eleanor, how are you? Hi, sweetheart
If a cat, okay.
Oh, cats are gonna fight, uh-oh, no fighting.
Fighting with, I had some cool dreams last night,
like some weird dreams.
First dream, I think I fell asleep to a blogger talking
and blogger that had dreamed like,
I was like hanging out with him and then like,
and he started like, you know, well.
He poor bombed his own stream. I'll just say it like that
So I saw everything but I know that's kind of funny and then I did a dream like where it's like I was like in this like woods
And I found all these books that I couldn't find before
and I would put there and stuff that I still have.
I need to find the books that I saw on the woods and stuff.
What else did I say?
If you're having trouble commenting,
just go ahead and go to my community wall
and say I'm blocked or something like that.
And I'll look into it.
A lot of people were blocked and no one's talking.
No one's even saying hello or anything.
It's weird.
They're just sitting there waiting for me
to do something.
Like I don't know.
Boo!
I don't know.
Also beep beep booboo kitty. Um, fuck you guys. I mean they they're like saying, oh, well, you know psyche
He must be he must be like some kind of weirdo now because you know, he's defending some of these people
Like let's let's delve into his past or we can make something up if it's not it's not there like it's like
It's like really get a life you motherfuckers. I mean it's like they're just sad sad people like you know
Just have kind of focus on yourselves and your own empowerment and your betterment rather than like trying to like
You know smear everybody else. Do you look better? It's you're not the Avengers. You're not fucking like, you know
You're basically the suicide squad, you know, that's that's what you know, you are and it's like not in a good way
You know, it's like you're you're fucking like really really
fucking picking on people and
You know hoping to cause these things and I know it's like sick. It's really sick
It's like, you know, and it's like, you know blood is on your hands for doing that to people
No, it's like and I'm sure I don't even know the victims of this of this like, you know
thing you're doing but
You're doing worse than anything anything that you're accusing anybody of because it's like you're like obviously killing spirits killing souls
You're like doing like seriously just the devil's work, you know
in a bad way.
So I don't know, it was my chat broken,
like no one can even say a word, they can say hello,
you can say fuck you, I don't know,
it would say something to me.
Like you're just gonna be silent really,
it's been like, you know, 10 minutes.
Okay, well, I'll just clear out the room basically
by just like, you know, I know who my friends are,
they would actually like my music and stuff,
so they would stay here for like a brand new song, you know,
so.
They don't demonetize, they demonize Turn your light into a warning sign
If you rise, they rewrite the lines Make it monster just to keep you dry
They don't wanna see you monetize Rather watch you out here, fight to survive
True burns, so they close their eyes Call you evil just to keep you quiet
If you like
Sure, they could suffice
you crazy if you don't coexist with the script they wrote for your whole life
tag break free once now they do the math how we stop them how we block this climb
turn this truth into a social crime now that people echo what they fail
Yeah, I'm not sure who it is, like, encouraging you not to talk.
Like, but if you are not talking, like, you're scared.
And why are you scared?
Like, why are you scared of these people?
You're afraid they'll do to you what they're
doing to everybody, other people?
Yeah, it can be scary, but it's like, you know,
have some balls, have some courage.
Like, you know, why are you?
Don't be afraid.
Fear is the fears of my killer. Good morning. Positively pause. I'm good to see you. Hey, there we go
Someone said hello, I know and I'm sorry if you get shit shipped right from somebody because of it
You know, and they're oh, you're in psychism just saying hello and not saying a fuck you or whatever, but it's like, you know
They're so sick of people being being like, you know bullied into silence and like, you know
They're trying to do it to me too like right now. They're like saying. Oh, well, let's a what's a funky time?
It's a little company. Yeah, you were hidden the other day
Like you're one of the people that both of you I think were hidden like I had a rogue mod going on hiding everybody
Because they can't even like have people like you know try to speak they have to like try to silence them and it's like really weird and creepy
Like especially the fact that they might have been a mod at one point
I think I knew who it was. Hey, I'm having a nice bagel stuff. You're looking into another page. You're listening to okay
Good, I know, but there are a lot of people here like no one's like talking to 20 people. There's two people talking
And then it's like the people are coming on the panel
Or basically like, you know, just here like, you know, poor mom or
So, you know, I'm you know what? It's like I'm not afraid of like, you know, being demonetized already happened
I'm not from not afraid of like, you know fucking
Being smeared already happened, right?
All already the worst is already happening. So am I afraid? No
I'm actually somebody that can stand up against it. And so I'm not afraid and I'm a book and I'll say what I want to say and I
Will say it without fear
Because everyone else is afraid and they're just jumping on bandwagons and going popular people and the popular people are just like these losers, right?
Basically silence everybody else
It's a dirty game, you gotta outplay them but not through like you know their
tactics which are just like smear tactics you just do it by the truth you
know keep telling the truth eventually someone will hear you when you have
people you don't like you just don't watch until they leave the panel yeah you
don't have to like everybody I mean you like spunky though right
People like to hate watch though. They love watching people that they hate sometimes, you know
Get them all angry
I mean, yeah, you love spunky. Mm-hmm. I
Don't hate watch. I don't really try to hate anybody. Hey, Brandon. Good morning to you. Good to see you
Yeah, but you know Brandon now they're now they're trying to do the same like they're like they're like looking
Trying to look into my past. Oh my god
Well, let's look at all his activity on every social network and try to figure something out and if it's not there
We'll like you know manufacturer
Like they're saying it right to my face. It's really obvious. I can show you the post later, but
It was beep beep and sweepy and all these people and beat his crew and stuff. Come on. I should know. How are you?
They just hate me they just hate me and they're like well if he's he's like
Saying these things he must have something like what's in his past like sweet pizza. I'll say in this like what did you do?
What did you do? What's your crime?
We're looking to my criminal history
They find a bunch of misdemeanors
Um, drug possession, nothing ever, ever, ever, ever anything, any accusation, anything violent
or anything.
And so, you know, if you're really so concerned, like go to a background check, I don't understand.
Like, um, but they're afraid to do that because I didn't print it up like nothing and then
that's, then they'll look even worse.
Crystal's video is exposing, yeah, you were yelling on the phone.
They don't have any evidence and it's like there's they're making shit up and like saying and plus even saying this pdf stuff
It's like there's nothing with any children or anything. It's like I don't understand
I don't know if it's controversial to say but it's like I think a 17 year old is not
Like a child like a young kid like I don't know. I mean, it's like they're young person, but I
Don't know and plus it there's no there's none. There's no there there and so
I don't know. It's like, you know, and it's even like saying like this is like, oh my gosh
You know, you're it's like I'm trying to like make
the point that it's like there's
There's a lot of like, you know, just like with I said with Benny like with Benny Blanco. Oh
Look at psyche's a sicko because he talks to Benny who's 24 year old. Oh
Yeah, and then yeah, so Aaron Carter did something like right
I heard you send nude pictures like a 14 year old or something like that, right? And it's like and they're all
Oh, he can do no wrong, you know, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, all right
They don't want that kind of stuff brought out in the light, right?
They make them a protector, right? Now, I don't know the whole story about that, but
Again, it's like the internet stuff is just a bunch of bullshit. I mean, it's like
it's a bunch of gotcha, it's a bunch of set ups,
it's a bunch of like,
and the culture is pushing it really hard,
like the culture is pushing this kind of stuff.
And so they're just like kind of a symptom of the culture.
And it's like, I mean, some people have been waiting
for this time, like where it's like, oh my gosh,
we're just gonna have, you know,
we're gonna start a new Holocaust for, you know,
these, I mean, it's like really sick.
It's like really sick.
Mm-hmm
People all these people can make these little truces and make these little agreements and
But like literally here's our game plan they're not they said they said let's listen to this and our group is like
You know, we're gaining traction. We have 3,000 people of crystals. So we're in like the crystal crystal and you know
anti-PDF group and then every other group is gonna look stupid because it's like
we're just gonna all smear everybody else and everybody else's group and
everyone's gonna leave those groups and join our group or or if they don't and
they had this whole they worked out their whole game plan and it's like it's
really sick it's really sick I don't know I heard that part of it yesterday
They're like, they're like, let's take everybody that that you know, he's like, okay Aldi was on the show and Aldi hates you
Right, but he likes you and he was nice tonight because he agrees with you about this
And so let's start doing this to like every person that hates you and bring all the people that hate you into this group
Based on this hate bonding over these other things, right?
And then everybody else is gonna
All their groups are gonna are gonna turn into these PDF supporting groups, but so stupid
So sick actually
You can hear the game plan. They're saying it like right out in front, right?
Yeah, who all he plays for night, you know video games are like
Like our generation grew up playing video games and so they still play video games and like certain games
It's like a little bit different than like, you know
Someone playing with you know Pokemon cards still or you Geo cards when they're you know in their 40s and stuff like that
But yeah, I don't know a little bit different. I think you know, which is like, you know, which somebody doesn't know when it has a problem with right, so I
Mean it's like adults have make these games, you know adults treat these games
So it's kind of like kind of like adult watching a Disney movie
It's like they're made for both adults
To enjoy because you know people have kids watching it and they don't want to be bored to death watching movies
So there's a lot of like jokes that are kind of like only adults would get
But I'm glad I don't have kids because I think it's a really difficult time to be raising
people this day and age and it's like, especially with all the accusations and flying around
and like people trying to get people taken away from it.
It's like really sad.
It's really sad actually.
And do you imagine there's a lot of like that, you know, and that chicken cakes came on and
Yesterday and the chicken cakes it's like
Trying to like smear this one person, but then it's like has no problem with another person, right? That's twice as bad
Right
Yeah, just I know Chris and a poor crystal. I mean this like crystal. What are these pictures of like a Disney?
You look like a Disney princess in your photos. You're wearing a crown
Here's it's this beautiful hot not gorgeous blonde woman and then it's like and then I've seen pictures of you and it's like
You don't look like that
Kind of look like that. You know you're kind of like
You look like a heavy a heavy woman from Alabama or something like that not to not to you know I
Don't know where you're from or whatever. I don't know you just like I don't know where your southern accent come from I
Just don't know. You know, I don't know where the fuck you cut your southern accent came from
So let's see. Yeah, I have another 20 minutes or maybe 10 minutes and then I'll go I'm gonna go get cigars
And maybe I'll be back on on but yeah, if anyone wants to
The chat or come on the panel. It's gonna be really quiet today, but you know, I'm gonna stand up for truth
I really recommend you can check out, you know, Alexander did a really good thing on
Analyzing a lot of this and getting into the nitty-gritty of like the background and the players and stuff like that and Alexander
You know, she
You know, she has
She's actually met crystal in real life, you know, she went and held baby Oliver, okay?
You know, if you know baby Oliver baby Oliver is one of the rubber babies the rubber babies are gone
She sold her pure babies her rubber babies that she cared so she sold baby Oliver for you know for money
you know, does anybody talk about that?
I mean, it's like, I don't know.
Baby Oliver, someone said,
Baby Oliver's now, he's grown up
and now he's a mannequin at Macy's or something like that.
And then everyone just laughed.
I mean, it's like, really?
Then how can we take it so seriously?
I mean, it's like so ridiculous.
But she had Alexandra hold one of the babies and stuff like that and and she's like and I was that and Alex said, you know
It felt like a real baby. Yeah, yeah
it was babies cost like a thousand dollars and
Because they're like supposed to be as realistic as possible to a real baby, but it looks like a dead baby
They basically me so it's kind of scared like weird and bizarre
But okay, whatever you want to do like whatever makes people feel better
Some people have had, you know traumas and stuff like that around it and so, you know
It makes them feel better, but it's just like a little bit bizarre to me and you know
Right
But it's like it just seems like it's just it's just like you can tell this guy
It's just like bull a bully, right?
And it's like it's just like everything to bully this person and it's like an excuse every other person's behavior, right?
But it's like he just like you can tell it's like and it is interesting that both the exact same age like always on their set
it's like it seems like there's like a competition or something like that and then this guy got some traction on it and
And and feels like you know superior or whatever and it's like I don't think so
So anyway, but
Anyway, I'm willing to like, you know take it down popular
Unpopular side because because popularity doesn't equal the truth, you know, and so I'm really looking for the truth about things
And I'll stand up for the truth no matter what you know
because
Being someone that's been slandered. I know how terrible it feels
Who said that all over is more cloud than 90% of the people okay, NorCal. That's actually funny
That's not actually funny thing you said
Maybe you're not such a bad guy after NorCal, you know, maybe you are just troll and you know
Don't mean harm and stuff like that. You are kind of a dick a little bit, but you know, maybe Oliver has 90% more cloud
Yeah
But um, okay, that's probably true
But you know now he's now he's now he's modeling at Macy's as an adult mannequin and so but um, I
Don't know. She's she's I heard that she sold those babies. Yeah, she had triplets
Oh, no, she had twins and then baby Oliver. It's just it's just so weird. It gets so weird
And she was actually on with, I think, like, you know, this woman, Barb Sawyer or something like that, and Barb was, like, she was, like,
talking about baby Oliver and Barb's like, I gotta go.
I gotta go now. She just couldn't talk about it, and normally it was getting too bizarre, right?
And it is kind of funny that it's so bizarre, but I don't know.
Arthur, you're taking a boycott against me?
Why am I, so Arthur, you, now Arthur is boycotting me, why?
Because you're gonna go to Crystal Land's show
because it's more popular right now.
Well, you understand, like, shows are always popular
when they start, because everyone wants to, like,
love bomb the show at first, and yeah, it's bizarre.
Yeah, you need, like, a realistic baby
is kind of weird to me, but I don't know.
We never know it's like dolls, you know, don't you just usually associate dolls with like, you know doing weird things. I don't know I
Collected these things all living dead dolls for a while then it got the guy got kind of too weird. Yeah, Arthur's a buddy troll. Yeah
Arthur is so nice to me, you know, he's always so friendly to me, but then it's like he says these way out things
Yeah
The fact that NorCal can talk and like not just kind of like say to me, oh, fuck you
You know you're sicko and stuff like that that you can actually just like talk and joke around that kind of tells me I
Don't know if it's buddy troll energy or whatever, but it's like or um, you know
At least he's like some kind of like like he's just he messes around online
It's not like fucking taking it too seriously, which is a good thing
It's all these people take it way too seriously, you know, I can appreciate that
Okay, oh, there we go. Yeah, he does doesn't he and so it's like you know, but but oh boy caught me right boy caught me
Even though there's 28 people here
You know and it's like my backup channel and you know
Even though no people are talking I think that people are wanting to hear what I have to say at least you know and
You know
do appreciate that, okay? So I'm gonna go, but yeah, so I'll be on a little bit
later. I hate to leave when there's like 30 people here, but it's still, I'm gonna
go, I'm gonna go get my coffee refill, get another coffee, and then I'm gonna get my
cigars, and then I'll be back, and I'll start a new panel, and we'll see what
happens then, okay? But thanks for coming this morning. We had breakfast, I ate my
bagel, I had my coffee, and then I got to get some more. So I'll talk to you a
little bit. Okay, see you guys. Thank you so much for coming.